

PROFILE

Energetic and compassionate individual committed to improving student learning experiences. Uses excellent curriculum knowledge to encourage, engage and inspire pupils to achieve learning goals. Approaches challenging situations with creativity and resourcefulness. Experienced teacher assistant with background in delivering successful strategic planning and policy formation. Committed to upholding school mission and values by analyzing student progress standards and addressing resulting challenges. Approachable leader with strong communication and interpersonal skills. Motivated teacher assistant with 8 years of progressive experience.

CONTACT

PHONE: 063 694 3695

ADDRESS: 648 Populier Avenue Breipaal, Douglas 8730

EMAIL: dawmoss07@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Team Leadership
- Teacher Support
- CAPS Curriculum
- Microsoft Office Suite expertise

DAWONE MOSS

Teacher

EDUCATION

Weslaan High School

2013 - 2015 Grade 12 Certificate

Boston City Campus and Business College

2017 - 2020

Diploma in Systems Development

Two Oceans Graduate Institute

2022 - 2022

Postgraduate Graduate in Education Economic and Management Science Senior Phase Computer Application Technology FET phase

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mulilo Mathematics Program - Manager

Jan 2024 - March 2024

- Managed team by offering support and constructive feedback to improve skills and maximize potential.
- Encouraging and engaging learners through after-school activities and competitions.
- Supported teacher with daily tasks such as homework correction, educational supply sourcing, and lesson planning.

Mulilo Mathematics Program - Senior Teacher Assistant

July 2020 - Dec 2023

- Lead class under supervision of teacher and teach lessons developed for taraeted academic enrichment.
- Assist mathematics teacher with all tasks required to smoothly run the class and effectively teach lessons to students.
- Achieve benchmark objectives identified for all teacher assistants by maintaining professional development and training standards.

DSEDC - Teacher Assistant

Jan 2016 - June 2020

- Developed educational materials for students ranging from primary to high school level and partnered with teachers to implement in classrooms.
- Worked in small groups with learners to provide better support.